Prince Prajapati

Cell (226) 202 4300

Princepn290@gmail.com



PROFILE

Technical Skills:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript/jQuery, MySQL, Python/Django, C#/ASP.NET, SDLC, API Build, Jira, Selenium, Postman, Unit Testing, UI/UX Design, Azure, Google Cloud

PROFILE SUMMARY

Highly organized and Developer and Blogger with over 1.5 years of experience in the coding development process. Understanding of machine learning, statistics, critical thinking with excellent practical experience using: Python, C#, JavaScript, MySQL. A result driven achiever with strong predictive modelling and data analytics skills.

Education: Conestoga College Institute

of Technology and LearningDiploma: Computer Programming

(Sept.2021-Apr.2023)

Employment:

Developer, Blogger: https://www.anonymous.education/ Jun 2020-Present

- Made this User-friendly blogger website by using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript using Visual Studio Code Editor as well WebStorm.
- Research and analyze the trending technology topics and implement in the website.
- Engineered and optimized 10+ web pages with advanced functionalities, resulting in a 40% increase in user engagement and a 25% decrease in bounce rate.
- Providing Code Structures and Solutions Python, Java and C languages.
- Implement Interviews for student to help in order to jump into Tech Industry.

Internship : Technical Analyst / <u>Gao Tek</u> ,Toronto, Canada/May 2022 – August 2022

- Coordinated with Level 1 technical support specialists to manage Agile, Azure DevOps, AWS Cloud as well Infrastructure administration of cloud.
- Solving almost 90% of technical issues, RFID and Network troubleshooting within joining.
- Provided web support and assisted customer with dept technical solutions at Tier 2 level.
- Promoted to Assistant Team leader to handle other Interns and trained them using Jira.
- Testing web pages using tools like Selenium and Postman, generate software tickets without reached out to level 3 engineers.

Projects:

Selenium Test

- Set-up the environment in Visual Studio to run tests on Selenium.
- Using Webdriver.io framework for Script Automation for Web Application.
- Track the code using Jira software to keep posted with team.
- Set up CI System, so it run the tests automatically on every execution.

Restaurant Management Project:

- Developed Management Project using JavaScript framework jQuery and SQL.
- Deploy to Android studio to make it available in Smart Phones.
- Handle exceptions of jQuery, validations and Google Search Console Analysis.
- Develop and implement Pipeline to initiate the Validation for web.